Department of Languages, Literature and Linguistics fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Faculty members, 1964 - 1983; F-13-3; 81 cm of textual records
  - Salaries and honoraria, 1965 - 1981; F-13-3-5; 7 cm of textual records
    - Salaries committee, 1976 - 1977; F-13-3-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 13-14)
    - Salaries committee, 1978 - 1981; F-13-3-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 13-14)
  - Tenure, promotion and renewal, 1968 - 1980; F-13-3-6; 10 cm of textual records
    - Tenure, promotion and renewal, 1972 - 1976; F-13-3-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-14)
    - Tenure committee, 1968; F-13-3-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-14)
    - Tenure committee, 1969; F-13-3-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-14)
    - Tenure committee, 1970; F-13-3-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 13-14)
    - Tenure committee, 1971; F-13-3-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 13-14)
    - Tenure committee, 1972; F-13-3-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 13-14)
    - Tenure committee, 1973; F-13-3-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
    - Tenure committee, 1974; F-13-3-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
    - Tenure committee, 1975; F-13-3-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
    - Tenure committee, 1976; F-13-3-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
    - Tenure committee, 1977; F-13-3-6-0-11 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
    - Tenure committee, 1978; F-13-3-6-0-12 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
    - Tenure committee, 1979; F-13-3-6-0-13 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
    - Tenure committee, 1980; F-13-3-6-0-14 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
  - Student complaints, 1975 - 1981; F-13-3-7; 1 cm of textual records
    - Complaints against faculty members, 1975 - 1981; F-13-3-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
    - Teaching evaluation, 1980; F-13-3-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
  - Faculty matters, 1976 - 1981; F-13-3-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-9)
- Faculty of Arts, 1980; F-13-4; 1 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the records relating to the relationship of the Department with the Faculty of Arts. It includes correspondence, memoranda, and reports.
  - Faculty of Arts, 1980; F-13-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
  - Annual reports, 1980; F-13-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
- University, 1973 - 1982; F-13-5; 11 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the relationship of the Department with interdisciplinary programs and other departments of the University, including the Computing Centre, Continuing Studies, and the Distance Education program. The series includes correspondence, memoranda and reports.
  - General, 1975 - 1979; F-13-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
  - Universities Council of B.C., 1977 - 1982; F-13-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
  - Grading practices, 1973 - 1977; F-13-5-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
  - Programs of Excellence, 1979; F-13-5-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
  - Strike policy, 1976; F-13-5-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
  - Distance education program, 1977; F-13-5-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
  - Law and social sciences, 1974; F-13-5-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
  - Continuing Studies, 1974 - 1975; F-13-5-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 13-15)
  - Continuing Studies, 1975 - 1980; F-13-5-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 13-16)
  - Faculty Association, 1978 - 1982; F-13-5-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 13-16)
  - Humanities, 1979; F-13-5-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 13-16)
  - Proposed policy changes, 1978 - 1980; F-13-5-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 13-16)
  - Computer Centre, 1979; F-13-5-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 13-16)
  - Student representation, 1979 - 1981; F-13-5-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 13-16)
- Student Affairs, 1970 - 1980; F-13-6; 2 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to student participation in departmental administration and student ethics. It includes correspondence, memoranda, and reports.
  - Student participation, 1975 - 1977; F-13-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-16)
  - Student ethics, 1970 - 1980; F-13-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-16)
- Miscellaneous, 1973 - 1981; F-13-7; 3 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the French Exchange program and the Committee on Language Articulation, and includes correspondence of the Chair of the Department. The series includes memoranda and reports.
  - Standing committee on language articulation, 1973 - 1978; F-13-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-16)
  - Personal correspondence, 1979 - 1981; F-13-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-16)
  - French exchange program, 1978; F-13-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-16)
- Departmental correspondence, 1969 - 1988; F-13-8; 14 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the Chair's correspondence relating to the administration of language programs. Records include correspondence and course and program proposals.
  The arrangement was provided by the archivist.
  No further accruals to the series are expected.
  Some files contain personal information; access to these files may be restricted to protect the privacy of individuals. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
  A file list is available.
  - German program correspondence, 1974 - 1987; F-13-8-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-17)
    Creator's original file classification code: 01-2.
  - German program SCAP submission, 1976 - 1978; F-13-8-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-17)
  - Letters supporting German - Fall, vol. 1, 1984; F-13-8-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-17)
  - Letters supporting German - Fall, vol. 2, 1984; F-13-8-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 13-17)
  - Chinese program, vol. 1, 1969 - 1973; F-13-8-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 13-17)
    Creator's original file classification code: 01-6.
  - Chinese program, vol. 2, 1974 - June 1977; F-13-8-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 13-17)
  - Chinese program, vol. 3, July 1977 - 1988; F-13-8-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 13-17)
  - Certificate in Chinese Studies, 1988; F-13-8-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: 01-6-1.
  - Other: Italian, Swahili, Hindi, Arabic, 1974 - 1988; F-13-8-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: 01-8.
  - Japanese, 1986 - 1988; F-13-8-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: 01-8-1.
  - Estonian Studies (GS 410, 86-1), 1983 - 1985; F-13-8-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
    Creator's original file classification code: 01-20.
- Course files, 1966 - 1977; F-13-9; 11 cm of textual records
  Series consists of course outlines for German, Chinese, Hindi, Italian and Latin. Series also include copies of examinations for French, German, Russian, and Spanish courses.
  The files are open with no restrictions.
  - German 100, 101 -- Introductory German, 1966 - 1975; F-13-9-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 102, 103 -- Introductory German, 1972 - 1975; F-13-9-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 105 -- Introduction in German Production, 1967 - 1968; F-13-9-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 201 -- Intermediate German, 1966 - 1975; F-13-9-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 202 -- Intermediate German II, 1967 - 1975; F-13-9-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 240 -- Introduction to German Literature I, 1972 - 1973; F-13-9-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 241 -- Introduction to German Literature II, 1972 - 1974; F-13-9-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 300 -- Richtlinien fur die Studenten, 1968 - 1974; F-13-9-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 301 -- Advanced German Composition I, 1968 - 1974; F-13-9-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 302 -- Advanced German, 1973 - 1974; F-13-9-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 340 -- A Survey of German Literature I, 1973 - 1974; F-13-9-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 341 -- A Survey of German Literature II, 1974 - 1976; F-13-9-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 401 -- Modern German: Phonology, 1972 - 1976; F-13-9-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 402 -- Modern German: Grammar, 1967 - 1975; F-13-9-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 403 -- History of the German Language I, [197-?] - [197-]; F-13-9-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 404 -- History of the German Language II, [197-?] - [197-]; F-13-9-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 405 -- Introduction to Germanic Linguistics, 1967 - 1974; F-13-9-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 440 -- German Literature, 1967 - 1969; F-13-9-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 441 -- German Literature, 1968 - 1969; F-13-9-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 443 -- German Literature, 1972 - 1975; F-13-9-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 444 -- Classicism, 1972 - 1974; F-13-9-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 445 -- Goethe's Faust, 1972 - 1974; F-13-9-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 446 -- Romanticism, 1973; F-13-9-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 447 -- 19th Century German Drama, 1973 - 1975; F-13-9-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 448 -- Drama in the 20th Century, 1972; F-13-9-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - German 460 -- German for Reading Knowledge, 1974; F-13-9-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - Chinese 100, 101, 341 -- Mandarin Chinese, 1970 - 1977; F-13-9-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - Hindi 100 -- Introduction to Hindi, 1966 - 1972; F-13-9-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - Italian 101 -- Introduction to Italian II, 1977; F-13-9-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - Latin 100 -- An Introductory course based on ancient authors, 1973 - 1975; F-13-9-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - Copies of examinations -- French, Russian, Spanish, 1966 - 1967; F-13-9-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 13-18)
  - Copies of examinations -- French, German, Russian, Spanish, 1968 - 1969; F-13-9-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 13-18)